<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="33">
    <author>Realismus Modding</author>
    <contributors>Rahkiin, baleBaron</contributors>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Seasons GEO: Northern Sweden</en>
        <de>Seasons GEO: Northern Sweden</de>
        <fr>Seasons GEO: Northern Sweden</fr>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Discover the colder climate of northern Sweden. Enjoy longer and harsher winters with snow and colder soil temperatures.

Northern Sweden is a GEO mod that simulates farming in subarctic regions.

The latest version of the Seasons mod is required.

Version 1.1.0.0
- Added Sugarcane (no growth)
- Updated calendar for Seasons 1.2]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Entdecke das kalte Klima in Nord Schweden. Genieße längere und härtere Winter mit Schnee und tieferen Bodentemperaturen.

Nord Schweden ist ein GEO mod, welcher das Klima in einer subarktischen Region simuliert.

Es wird die neuste Version vom Seasons mod benötigt.

Version 1.1.0.0
- Zuckerrohr hinzugefügt
- Kalender aktualisiert für Seasons 1.2]]></de>

        <it><![CDATA[Scopri il clima freddo della Svezia settentrionale. Godetevi gli inverni più lunghi e rigidi con neve e basse temperature del terreno.

Northern Sweden è una GEO mod che simula l'agricoltura nelle regioni subartiche.

È richiesta l'ultima versione della Seasons Mod.]]></it>
        <fr><![CDATA[Découvrez le climat le plus froid du nord de la Suède. Profitez d'hivers plus longs et plus durs, avec de la neige et des températures du sol plus froides.

Le mod GEO Nord de la Suède simule l'agriculture dans les régions subarctiques.

La dernière version du mod Seasons est nécessaire.

Version 1.1.0.0
- Canne à sucre ajoutée
- Calendrier mis à jour pour Seasons 1.2]]></fr>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <seasons version="2">
        <dataFolder>data/</dataFolder>
        <type>geo</type>
    </seasons>

    <inputBindings>
    </inputBindings>
</modDesc>
