<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="33">
    <author>Realismus Modding</author>
    <contributors>reallogger</contributors>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Seasons GEO: Wales</en>
        <de>Seasons GEO: Wales</de>
        <fr>Seasons GEO: Wales</fr>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[A mild wet climate characterizes the weather of Wales. With short amount of proper harvesting time and a lot of rainy days, you will have to plan carefully and work hard to keep your farm afloat.

Wales is a GEO mod for Seasons that simulates farming in Wales region.

The latest version of the Seasons mod is required.

Version 1.1.0.0
- Added Sugarcane (no growth)
- Updated calendar for Seasons 1.2]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Für Wales ist ein mild nasses Wetter charakteristisch. Mit einem kleinen Zeitraum für die Ernte und vielen Regentagen musst du gut planen und hart arbeiten, um deinen Hof flott zu halten.

Wales ist ein GEO mod, welcher das Klima in Wales simuliert.

Es wird die neuste Version vom Seasons mod benötigt.

Version 1.1.0.0
- Zuckerrohr hinzugefügt
- Kalender aktualisiert für Seasons 1.2]]></de>
        <it><![CDATA[Un clima mite ed umido caratterizza il meteo del Galles. Con piccole finestre temporali per trebbiare e molti giorni piovosi, dovrai pianificare con cura e lavorare sodo per mantenere la tua farm attiva.

Galles è una GEO mod per Seasons che simula l'agricoltura nelle regioni inglesi del Galles.

È richiesta l'ultima versione della Seasons Mod.]]></it>
        <fr><![CDATA[Un climat doux et humide caractérise la météo du Pays de Galles. Avec un temps court pour les récoltes et beaucoup de jours pluvieux, vous devrez planifier soigneusement et travailler dur pour garder votre ferme à flot.

Le Pays de Galles est un mod GEO pour Seasons qui simule l'agriculture dans la région du Pays de Galles.

La dernière version du mod Seasons est nécessaire.

Version 1.1.0.0
- Canne à sucre ajoutée (pas de croissance)
- Calendrier mis à jour pour Seasons 1.2]]></fr>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>

    <credits><![CDATA[
## Translations
German - Blaggy, Amadeo
Italian - *TurboStar*
French - Farmer1602
]]></credits>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <seasons version="2">
        <type>geo</type>
        <dataFolder>data/</dataFolder>
    </seasons>
</modDesc>
