<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="33">
    <author>Realismus Modding</author>
    <contributors>Rahkiin, theSeb, reallogger</contributors>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Seasons GEO: Central France</en>
        <de>Seasons GEO: Central France</de>
        <fr>Seasons GEO: Central France</fr>
        <it>Seasons GEO: Central France</it>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Do you want to experience agriculture in the center of France? Try your luck in the Orléans region in the heart of the Beauce, the grain loft of France.

The Beauceron climate is relatively stable, oceanic degraded and dry. Thus, although the winters are generally gray and cool (0 / + 10 ° C), the summers are warm, dry and sunny, allowing for many crops

The latest version of the Seasons mod is required.]]></en>
        <fr><![CDATA[Voulez-vous faire l'expérience de l'agriculture au centre de la France? Tentez votre chance dans la région d'Orléans en plein coeur de la Beauce, le grenier à grain de la France.

Le climat Beauceron est relativement stable, océanique dégradé et sec. Ainsi, même si les hivers sont globalement gris et frais ( 0 / +10°C), les étés sont assez chauds, secs et ensoleillés permettant de nombreuses cultures

La dernière version du mod Seasons est nécessaire.]]></fr>
        <de><![CDATA[Möchtest Du die Landwirtschaft im Loire-Tal in Zentralfrankreich erleben?

MISSING

Es wird die neuste Version vom Seasons mod benötigt.]]></de>
        <it><![CDATA[Vuoi sperimentare l'agricoltura nel centro della Francia? Prova la tua fortuna nella regione di Orléans, nel cuore del Beauce, il granaio di Francia.

Il clima di Beauceron è relativamente stabile, oceanico degradato e asciutto. Quindi, anche se gli inverni sono generalmente grigi e freschi (0 / + 10 ° C), le estati sono calde, secche e soleggiate, consentendo molte colture

È necessaria l'ultima versione del mod Seasons.]]></it>
    </description>

    <credits><![CDATA[
## Translations

German - Amadeo
French - Farmer1602]]></credits>

    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <seasons version="2">
        <type>geo</type>
        <dataFolder>data/</dataFolder>
    </seasons>
</modDesc>
